[
  {
    "question": "Servant",
    "dragonAnswer": "2r",
    "answer": "Aar"
  },
  {
    "question": "Beautiful",
    "dragonAnswer": "Brit",
    "answer": "Brit"
  },
  {
    "question": "Undead",
    "dragonAnswer": "D6l",
    "answer": "Diil"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hound",
    "dragonAnswer": "Dok",
    "answer": "Dok"
  },
  {
    "question": "Lord",
    "dragonAnswer": "Drog",
    "answer": "Drog"
  },
  {
    "question": "Carve",
    "dragonAnswer": "Dw6rok",
    "answer": "Dwiirok"
  },
  {
    "question": "Extinguish",
    "dragonAnswer": "Even2r",
    "answer": "Evenaar"
  },
  {
    "question": "Haunt",
    "dragonAnswer": "Fol9k",
    "answer": "Folook"
  },
  {
    "question": "Stamina",
    "dragonAnswer": "G2n",
    "answer": "Gaan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Wolf",
    "dragonAnswer": "Groh6k",
    "answer": "Grohiik"
  }
]